In this lesson, we'll learn about automating our machine-learning workflows with
在本课程中 我们要学习一个案例
pipelines using this dataset on corporate messaging as a case study.
对企业信息通过管道技术搭建机器学习工作流
This is one of the free datasets provided on the figure-eight platform.
这是 figure 8 平台上免费提供的一个数据集
Each row contains information about a social media post from
每行包含一个公司发布的社交网络帖子
different corporations and contains a column for the category of the post.
以及一列表示该帖子的类别
If we look at the value counts for this category column,
如果你查看对该类别列用 value_counts 计数的结果
we can see that each post is classified as information,
我们可以看到每个帖子被分成信息 (information)
action, dialogue or exclude.
行动 (action) 对话 (dialogue) 或其他 (exclude)
If we look back on the figure-eight site,
如果查看 figure 8 网站
we can find a description of each category.
我们可以看到每个类别的描述
Information, objective statements about the company or its activities,
信息 (Information) 是该公司或它的活动的客观描述
dialogue like replies to users or
对话 (dialogue) 是对用户的回复
action such as messages that ask for votes or ask users to click on links.
行动 (action) 是指类似要求投票或者要求用户点击链接的消息
Information seems to be the most common category by far followed by
信息 (Information) 目前看起来是出现频率最高的
action and then dialogue and exclude seems to be a miscellaneous column.
然后是行动 (action)  之后是对话 (dialogue)  最后是其他 (exclude)
Also notice that we have a category confidence column.
还要注意 我们有一列表示置信程度 (confidence)
Since we're only interested in rows classified into one
因为我们仅仅对那些以很高置信程度
of these top three categories with full confidence,
被分到前三类的行感兴趣
we're going to narrow down to rows with a confidence of
我们将只关注置信程度为 1 的
one and category that is not exclude.
被分类为非“其他”类的那些行
Awesome. This is what we have left.
很棒这是满足条件的
Now, let's isolate the columns to be used as
现在 让我们将要在分类器中用作特征和标签的列
features and labels in this classifier and convert them to NumPy arrays.
分离出来并转换为 NumPy 数组 (array)
Here, those would be the text column and the category column.
这里 就是文本 (text) 列和类别 (category) 列
Here's the first row of text data and the category for that first row.
这是文本列的第一行 以及第一行的类别
To repeat the transformations made on this dataset,
因为要重复这个数据集的转换过程
here are steps in a nice,
所以这是一个写好的 load_data 函数
low data function that we'll use for the rest of our lesson.
我们会在后续的课程中使用
Let's try it out. Now our dataset has 2,403 rows of corporate messaging data.
运行一下现在 我们的数据集有 2,403 行的公司消息数据